[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 21, "question": "You never did that, did you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "did", "that", ",", "did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 22, "answer": "I did a couple of the love scenes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "a", "couple", "of", "the", "love", "scenes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 37, "question": "Could you have ever imagined, when you were out there embedded with these troops, that that would happen?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "you", "have", "ever", "imagined", ",", "when", "you", "were", "out", "there", "embedded", "with", "these", "troops", ",", "that", "that", "would", "happen", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "IN", "DT", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 38, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 60, "question": "It is just a total distraction, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "just", "a", "total", "distraction", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 61, "answer": "It is.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, I don't think the idea -- the problem is that General Petraeus had an affair.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "the", "idea", "--", "the", "problem", "is", "that", "General", "Petraeus", "had", "an", "affair", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Sunday"], "PERSON": ["George Stephanopoulos"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "``", "DT", "NNP", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 91, "question": "What do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 92, "answer": "First of all, I was substituting for George Stephanopoulos that Sunday as host of \"This Week.\"", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "was", "substituting", "for", "George", "Stephanopoulos", "that", "Sunday", "as", "host", "of", "``", "This", "Week", ".", "''"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 108, "question": "Did she act in good faith, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "she", "act", "in", "good", "faith", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 109, "answer": "I can't get inside her brain.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "get", "inside", "her", "brain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["White House"], "LOCATION": ["Benghazi"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBG", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "That's a problem, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "a", "problem", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Without question, as somebody who was covering the Benghazi story in the months leading up to the election, and also covering the election, it was so politicized with the White House and the administration in a defensive crouch, because they thought every word they said would be twisted and unfairly attacked.", "answer_tokens": ["Without", "question", ",", "as", "somebody", "who", "was", "covering", "the", "Benghazi", "story", "in", "the", "months", "leading", "up", "to", "the", "election", ",", "and", "also", "covering", "the", "election", ",", "it", "was", "so", "politicized", "with", "the", "White", "House", "and", "the", "administration", "in", "a", "defensive", "crouch", ",", "because", "they", "thought", "every", "word", "they", "said", "would", "be", "twisted", "and", "unfairly", "attacked", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 135, "question": "How are you?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 136, "answer": "Thanks, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["Thanks", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 170, "question": "Do you think it's healthy for a biographer to be that close to their subject?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "healthy", "for", "a", "biographer", "to", "be", "that", "close", "to", "their", "subject", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "PRP$", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 171, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 194, "question": "But what would have happened, for example -- with one of your subjects, JFK -- what would have happened to JFK if e-mail and text messaging had existed?", "question_tokens": ["But", "what", "would", "have", "happened", ",", "for", "example", "--", "with", "one", "of", "your", "subjects", ",", "JFK", "--", "what", "would", "have", "happened", "to", "JFK", "if", "e-mail", "and", "text", "messaging", "had", "existed", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "NN", ":", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ":", "WP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "VBG", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 195, "answer": "ELLEY: Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["ELLEY", ":", "Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["JFK", "JFK"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Does it matter if they have affairs?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "it", "matter", "if", "they", "have", "affairs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "I think that's such a great question.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "'s", "such", "a", "great", "question", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 223, "question": "Like whom?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "whom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 224, "answer": "Eliot Spitzer would come to mind.", "answer_tokens": ["Eliot", "Spitzer", "would", "come", "to", "mind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 260, "question": "How about Churchill?", "question_tokens": ["How", "about", "Churchill", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 261, "answer": "I don't think Churchill ever had affairs.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "Churchill", "ever", "had", "affairs", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 313, "question": "Why were you not a fan of General Petraeus?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "were", "you", "not", "a", "fan", "of", "General", "Petraeus", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 314, "answer": "Well, the American media has come up with this narrative that he's the American hero who betrayed by the woman.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "American", "media", "has", "come", "up", "with", "this", "narrative", "that", "he", "'s", "the", "American", "hero", "who", "betrayed", "by", "the", "woman", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 356, "question": "Were you surprised when Petraeus got the CIA job?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "surprised", "when", "Petraeus", "got", "the", "CIA", "job", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 357, "answer": "I was worried about it because he's created again -- the military crossing into the CIA is very dangerous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "worried", "about", "it", "because", "he", "'s", "created", "again", "--", "the", "military", "crossing", "into", "the", "CIA", "is", "very", "dangerous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["CIA"], "PERSON": ["Petraeus"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["England"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 369, "question": "-- for him to resign?", "question_tokens": ["--", "for", "him", "to", "resign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 370, "answer": "In England, it is.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "England", ",", "it", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 384, "question": "That is quite dangerous, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "quite", "dangerous", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 385, "answer": "Very dangerous.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "dangerous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 416, "question": "On balance, are you pleased though that he won the election?", "question_tokens": ["On", "balance", ",", "are", "you", "pleased", "though", "that", "he", "won", "the", "election", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 417, "answer": "I'm pleased he won the election.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "pleased", "he", "won", "the", "election", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Why did you want to make this series?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "did", "you", "want", "to", "make", "this", "series", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "Boy.", "answer_tokens": ["Boy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 514, "question": "You thought it was really good?", "question_tokens": ["You", "thought", "it", "was", "really", "good", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 515, "answer": "I think he is tremendous.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "he", "is", "tremendous", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "You never did that, did you?", "question_tokens": ["You", "never", "did", "that", ",", "did", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "I did a couple of the love scenes.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "did", "a", "couple", "of", "the", "love", "scenes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "Of all the Bond girls, and there were so many, especially in the seven movies you made, if I could trap you on a desert island with one of them, and I know it is like choosing your favorite baby, but if I can put you on an island for the rest of your life with one Bond girl, who would it be?", "question_tokens": ["Of", "all", "the", "Bond", "girls", ",", "and", "there", "were", "so", "many", ",", "especially", "in", "the", "seven", "movies", "you", "made", ",", "if", "I", "could", "trap", "you", "on", "a", "desert", "island", "with", "one", "of", "them", ",", "and", "I", "know", "it", "is", "like", "choosing", "your", "favorite", "baby", ",", "but", "if", "I", "can", "put", "you", "on", "an", "island", "for", "the", "rest", "of", "your", "life", "with", "one", "Bond", "girl", ",", "who", "would", "it", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "DT", "NNP", "VBZ", ",", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "I'd actually go with my wife.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'d", "actually", "go", "with", "my", "wife", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "``", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "''", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "I can say \"I love you\" in Swedish.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "can", "say", "``", "I", "love", "you", "''", "in", "Swedish", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "``", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "''", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "I mean, to walk around with people knowing you're Bond?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "to", "walk", "around", "with", "people", "knowing", "you", "'re", "Bond", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "But you get sort of used to it after you have said, \"my name is Bond, James Bond\" 400 times.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "you", "get", "sort", "of", "used", "to", "it", "after", "you", "have", "said", ",", "``", "my", "name", "is", "Bond", ",", "James", "Bond", "''", "400", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NNS", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 551, "question": "Do people make you still say that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "people", "make", "you", "still", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 552, "answer": "Oh, yes, always.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "yes", ",", "always", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "Everywhere you go?", "question_tokens": ["Everywhere", "you", "go", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Every interview.", "answer_tokens": ["Every", "interview", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 555, "question": "How many women do you think you have seduced because you played James Bond in the last 50 years?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "women", "do", "you", "think", "you", "have", "seduced", "because", "you", "played", "James", "Bond", "in", "the", "last", "50", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 556, "answer": "Been married four times.", "answer_tokens": ["Been", "married", "four", "times", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["James Bond"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 567, "question": "So you always just this nice, calm figure?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "always", "just", "this", "nice", ",", "calm", "figure", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 568, "answer": "I try to be.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "try", "to", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "WP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 571, "question": "Have you been what British people would describe as a bit of a naughty boy over the years, would you say?", "question_tokens": ["Have", "you", "been", "what", "British", "people", "would", "describe", "as", "a", "bit", "of", "a", "naughty", "boy", "over", "the", "years", ",", "would", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBN", "WP", "NNP", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 572, "answer": "Depends what the definition of naughty is.", "answer_tokens": ["Depends", "what", "the", "definition", "of", "naughty", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "IN", "CC", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "What would your definition be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "your", "definition", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "NN", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "I suppose getting drunk, falling over and waking up in strange hotel rooms.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "getting", "drunk", ",", "falling", "over", "and", "waking", "up", "in", "strange", "hotel", "rooms", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 577, "question": "Do you have any regrets in your 85 years?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "regrets", "in", "your", "85", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 578, "answer": "I regret I can't start them all again.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "regret", "I", "ca", "n't", "start", "them", "all", "again", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Are you surprised that the Bond franchise is still so successful?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "that", "the", "Bond", "franchise", "is", "still", "so", "successful", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "You didn't hold that book up high enough.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "did", "n't", "hold", "that", "book", "up", "high", "enough", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 594, "question": "Are you surprised that it still -- I mean, even more successful than it was 50 years ago?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "that", "it", "still", "--", "I", "mean", ",", "even", "more", "successful", "than", "it", "was", "50", "years", "ago", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RBR", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 595, "answer": "No, not really.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "not", "really", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 607, "question": "You a fan of Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["You", "a", "fan", "of", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 608, "answer": "I'm not going to answer anything political.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "answer", "anything", "political", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["UNICEF", "United Nations"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "."], "qSentId": 609, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 610, "answer": "Because I work with UNICEF and you're not allowed with the United Nations.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "I", "work", "with", "UNICEF", "and", "you", "'re", "not", "allowed", "with", "the", "United", "Nations", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Reagan"]}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 613, "question": "Do you feel that when you travel the world?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "feel", "that", "when", "you", "travel", "the", "world", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 614, "answer": "Yes, I think that he, like Reagan, makes an American proud to be an American.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "think", "that", "he", ",", "like", "Reagan", ",", "makes", "an", "American", "proud", "to", "be", "an", "American", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "If I could give you five minutes back of your entire life, and it can't involve marriage or children to relive, the greatest moment of your life, what would you choose?", "question_tokens": ["If", "I", "could", "give", "you", "five", "minutes", "back", "of", "your", "entire", "life", ",", "and", "it", "ca", "n't", "involve", "marriage", "or", "children", "to", "relive", ",", "the", "greatest", "moment", "of", "your", "life", ",", "what", "would", "you", "choose", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "TO", "VB", ",", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "I suppose being with my parents when I did something that was worthwhile.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "being", "with", "my", "parents", "when", "I", "did", "something", "that", "was", "worthwhile", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 619, "question": "Getting their love and respect?", "question_tokens": ["Getting", "their", "love", "and", "respect", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 620, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 625, "question": "What would he have made of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "he", "have", "made", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 626, "answer": "He was very happy.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "was", "very", "happy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121118pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 632, "question": "That's basically been the story of your life ever since, isn't it, Sir Roger?", "question_tokens": ["That", "'s", "basically", "been", "the", "story", "of", "your", "life", "ever", "since", ",", "is", "n't", "it", ",", "Sir", "Roger", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RB", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 633, "answer": "Outnumbered.", "answer_tokens": ["Outnumbered", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Roger"]}}]